dear customer I am an ICI Bank
representative and I'm going to take you
through an incredibly easy journey of
video kyc for your personal loan so
let's begin log in with the link which
you have received for video kyc on both
SMS and email before you open the link
please ensure that you are in a strong
Network area or have a good Wi-Fi
connectivity on your device also follow
a few instructions for smooth process
keep original pan card a blank paper and
a black pen for Signature along with you
while doing the video
kyc look into the camera while verifying
the
details while capturing the photo make
sure you're in a proper attire with
white background proper lighting and
keep your eyes open do not show AAR card
or share your AAR number during the
call also no third person should visible
or audible during the call now once you
have opened the link you will get an OTP
through a SMS and an email to log to the
video kyc portal after entering the OTP
please click on login then you will see
a video kyc option click on the same to
initiate the video kyc call after this
you will see a popup with video kyc
instructions click on okay the next
screen will show you your name and your
your pan number you will need to enter
your Adar number and accept the terms
and conditions then click on verify now
only once and wait for the Adar OTP to
be received on your Adar linked mobile
number please avoid multiple clicks and
ensure that the mobile number linked to
Adar is active as you will receive an
OTP triggered by uidai on it enter the
OTP and click on continue then your Adar
photo and address will be fetched from
uidai please confirm that your address
details and current address as per the
application form are correct by ticking
after confirmation you need to click on
initiate video kyc button only once and
wait for the web page to load please
avoid multiple
clicks after initiation the system will
connect you to an agent request you to
wait till you connect to the agent when
you are connected to the agent you will
see a chat window and the agent will
initiate a two-way video call please
accept it when the video call starts the
agent will ask you to share your
location and other verification
parameters please note that you need to
be in India while initiating video
kyc the agent will guide you through the
rest of the process and that is your
video kyc Journey yes it's as simple as
that with ICICI Bank